<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.SymbolEditor.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>GFDL-1.2-without-invariant</metadata_license>
  <name>SymbolEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">SymbolEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">SymbolEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">SymbolEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">SymbolEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">SymbolEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">SymbolEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Sümbolite redaktor</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Ikur Editorea</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">SymbolEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">SymbolEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">SymbolEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">SymbolEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">SymbolEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">SymbolEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">SymbolEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">SymbolEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">EdytorSymboli</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Editor de Símbolos</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Editor de Símbolos</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">SymbolEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">SymbolEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">SymbolEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Symboleditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">SymbolEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">SymbolEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxSymbolEditorxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">符号编辑器</name>
  <summary>A cross stitch symbol editor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Un editor de símbols de punt de creu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Un editor de símbols de punt de creu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Editor symbolů pro vyšívání křížkovým stehem</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Ein Kreuzstich-Symboleditor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">A cross stitch symbol editor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Un editor de símbolos de punto de cruz</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Tikkimispistete sümbolite redaktor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Gurutze-puntuko ikurren editore bat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Ristipistosymbolimuokkain</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Un éditeur de symbole au point de croix</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Un editor de símbolos de cruz en punta</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Sebuah editor simbol kristik (cross stitch)</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Un editor di simboli punto croce</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">십자수 기호 편집기</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Een kruissteeksymboolbewerker</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Redigeringsprogram for krossting</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Edytor symboli Cross Stitch.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Um editor de símbolos de pontos de cruz</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Um editor de símbolos em ponto cruz</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Editor symbolov krížových stehov</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Urejevalnik križnih šivov</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">En symboleditor för korsstygn</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Çapraz köşe sembol düzenleyicisi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Програма для редагування позначок для вишивання хрестиком</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxA cross stitch symbol editorxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>SymbolEditor is a program that can create libraries of QPainterPath objects with hints on how to render them. It was originally designed to create symbol libraries for the KXStitch application, but other applications using similar functionality could also make use of them. There are a number of tools to aid the designing of symbols, including lines, bezier curves, rectangle and ellipse. Text characters can be selected from any font and the symbols can be mirrored or rotated. Symbols can be filled or unfilled, the line end type and joining style can be changed and the line thickness can be varied.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El SymbolEditor és un programa que pot crear biblioteques d'objectes «QPainterPath» amb consells quant a representar-los. Originalment va ser dissenyada per a crear biblioteques de símbols per a l'aplicació KXStitch, però altres aplicacions que usin funcionalitats similars també en poden fer ús. Hi ha diverses eines per a ajudar a dissenyar els símbols, incloent-hi línies, corbes de bezier, rectangles i el·lipses. Els caràcters de text es poden seleccionar des de qualsevol tipus de lletra i els símbols es poden emmirallar o girar. Els símbols es poden farcir o no farcir, el tipus de final de línia i l'estil d'unió es poden canviar i es pot variar el gruix de les línies.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El SymbolEditor és un programa que pot crear biblioteques d'objectes «QPainterPath» amb consells quant a representar-los. Originalment va ser dissenyada per a crear biblioteques de símbols per a l'aplicació KXStitch, però altres aplicacions que usin funcionalitats similars també en poden fer ús. Hi ha diverses eines per a ajudar a dissenyar els símbols, incloent-hi línies, corbes de bezier, rectangles i el·lipses. Els caràcters de text es poden seleccionar des de qualsevol tipus de lletra i els símbols es poden emmirallar o girar. Els símbols es poden farcir o no farcir, el tipus de final de línia i l'estil d'unió es poden canviar i es pot variar el gruix de les línies.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">SymbolEditor ist ein Programm, das Bibliotheken von QPainterPath-Objekten erstellen kann mit Hinweisen, wie sie zu rendern sind. Es wurde ursprünglich entwickelt, um Symbolbibliotheken für die Anwendung KXStitch zu erstellen, aber auch andere Anwendungen, die eine ähnliche Funktionalität verwenden, können davon Gebrauch machen. Es gibt eine Reihe von Werkzeuge, die bei der Gestaltung von Symbolen helfen, darunter Linien, Bézier-Kurven Rechteck und Ellipse. Die Textzeichen können aus einer beliebigen Schriftart ausgewählt werden und die Symbole können gespiegelt oder gedreht werden. Symbole können gefüllt oder ungefüllt sein, der Linienende und der Verbindungsstil können geändert werden und die Linienstärke kann variiert werden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">SymbolEditor is a program that can create libraries of QPainterPath objects with hints on how to render them. It was originally designed to create symbol libraries for the KXStitch application, but other applications using similar functionality could also make use of them. There are a number of tools to aid the designing of symbols, including lines, bezier curves, rectangle and ellipse. Text characters can be selected from any font and the symbols can be mirrored or rotated. Symbols can be filled or unfilled, the line end type and joining style can be changed and the line thickness can be varied.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">SymbolEditor es un programa que puede crear bibliotecas de objetos de QPainterPath que sugiere cómo se muestran. Originalmente se diseñó para crear bibliotecas de símbolos para la aplicación KXStitch, pero también la pueden usar otras aplicaciones de funcionalidad similar. Existen diversas herramientas para ayudar a crear símbolos, que incluyen líneas, curvas de bezier, rectángulos y elipses. Puede seleccionar caracteres de texto de cualquier tipo de letra y los símbolos se pueden reflejar y rotar. Puede crear símbolos rellenos o sin rellenar, cambiar los remates y las juntas, y variar el grosor de líneas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Sümbolite redaktor on rakendus QPainterPath'i objektide teekide loomiseks koos vihjetega, kuidas neid renderdada. Algupäraselt oli see mõeldud rakendusele KXStitch sümboliteekide loomiseks, kuid seda võivad edukalt kasutada ka teised sarnase funktsionaalsusega rakendused. Sümbolite loomisel on abiks hulk tööriistu, sealhulgas sirgjooned, Bezier kõverad, ristkülikud ja ellipsid. Tekstimärke võib valida mis tahes fondist ning sümboleid võib peegeldada või pöörata. Sümbolid võivad olla täidetud või täitmata, joonetipu tüüpi ja ühendusestiili saab muuta, samuti võib varieerida joone jämedust.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">SymbolEditor, ikur editorea, QPainterPath objektuen liburutegiak, haiek errendatzeko argibideekin, sor ditzakeen programa bat da. Jatorrian KXStitch aplikaziorako ikur-liburutegiak sortzeko diseinatu zen, baino antzeko funtzioak erabiltzen dituzten beste aplikazio batzuek ere erabil dezakete. Ikurrak diseinatzen laguntzeko tresna batzuk daude, hala nola bezier-kurbak, laukizuzena eta elipsea. Testu-karaktereak edozein letra-tipotatik hauta daitezke eta ikurrak ispilatu edo biratu daitezke. Ikurrak beteta edo bete gabe izan daitezke, lerroaren errematea eta lotura-estiloa alda daitezke baita lerroaren lodiera ere.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">SymbolEditor on ohjelma, jolla luoda QPainterPath-olioita vihjein niiden hahmontamisesta. Se suunniteltiin alkuaan KXStitch-sovelluksen symbolikirjastojen luomiseen, mutta myös muut samanlaiset ohjelmat voivat hyötyä siitä. Symbolien suunnitteluun on joukko työkaluja kuten viiva, bezierkäyrä, nelikulmio ja ellipsi. Tekstimerkit voi valita mistä vain fontista, ja symboleja voi peilata ja kiertää. Symbolit voivat olla täytettyjä tai ääriviivasymboleja, viivan pääte- ja liitostyyppiä voi vaihtaa ja viivan paksuutta vaihdella.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Le programme SymbolEditor peut créer des bibliothèques d'objets « QPainterPath » avec des conseils sur comment les réaliser. Il a été initialement conçu pour créer des bibliothèques de symboles pour l'application « KXStitch », mais d'autres applications utilisant des fonctionnalités similaires peuvent aussi les utiliser. Il y a un certain nombre d'outils pour la conception de symboles, incluant, les lignes, les courbes de Bézier, les rectangles et les ellipses. Les caractères peuvent aussi être sélectionnés à partir de n'importe quelle police de caractères et les symboles peuvent être transformés par effet de miroir ou de rotation. Les symboles peuvent être pleins ou non pleins. Les types de fin de ligne et les styles de fusion peuvent être modifiés et l'épaisseur de lignes peuvent être variables.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">SymbolEditor é un programa que pode crear bibliotecas de obxectos QPainterPath con información sobre como renderizalos. Deseñouse orixinalmente para crear bibliotecas de símbolos para a aplicación KXStitch, pero outros programas cunha funcionalidade similar poderían tamén usar ditas bibliotecas. Hai un bo número de ferramentas para axudar no deseño dos símbolos, como liñas, curvas bezier, rectángulos e elipses. Poden seleccionarse caracteres de texto de calquera tipo de letra, e os símbolos poden repetirse sobre un eixo (efecto espello) ou rotarse. Os símbolos poden encherse opcionalmente, pode cambiarse o estilo do final das liñas e os nodos de unión entre liñas, e pode cambiarse a anchura das liñas, combinando distintos valores en distintas liñas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">SymbolEditor adalah sebuah program yang bisa menciptakan pustaka objek QPainterPath dengan petunjuk pada bagaimana cara merendernya. Yang mana didesain secara original untuk menciptakan pustaka simbol buat aplikasi KXStitch. Namun aplikasi lain menggunakan fungsionalitas mirip yang juga menggunakannya. Ada beberapa alat yang dapat membantu mendesain simbol, termasuk garis, kurva bezier, persegi, dan jorong. Karakter teks dapat dipilih dari font apapun dan simbol dapat dicerminkan atau dirotasikan. Simbol dapat terisi atau takterisi, tipe ujung garis dan gaya penggabungan bisa diubah dan tutul baris bisa divariasi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">SymbolEditor è un programma che può creare librerie di oggetti QPainterPath con suggerimenti su come renderizzarli. Era stato originariamente progettato per creare librerie di simboli per KXStitch, ma può essere usato anche da altre applicazioni che fanno uso di funzionalità simili. Ci sono una serie di strumenti per aiutare nel disegno di simboli, incluse linee, curve di Bezier, rettangoli ed ellissi. I caratteri di testo possono essere selezionati da qualsiasi font, e i simboli possono essere rispecchiati e ruotati. I simboli possono essere riempiti o svuotati, i tipi di fine linea e gli stili di unione possono essere cambiati, e lo spessore della linea può essere variato.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">SymbolEditor는 렌더링 힌트 정보와 같이 QPainterPath 객체 라이브러리를 만드는 프로그램입니다. 원래는 KXStitch 프로그램의 기호 라이브러리 제작 용도로 개발했지만, 비슷한 기능을 사용하는 다른 프로그램에서도 사용할 수 있습니다. 직선, 베지어 곡선, 직사각형, 타원형 등의 기호를 디자인할 때 사용할 수 있는 도구가 있습니다. 임의의 글꼴에서 텍스트 글자를 선택할 수 있으며 기호를 대칭시키거나 회전시킬 수 있습니다. 기호의 내부를 채우거나 비워 둘 수 있으며, 선 끝 종류와 합치기 스타일을 변경할 수 있으며 선 굵기를 변경할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">SymbolEditor is een programma dat bibliotheken van QPainterPath-objecten kan maken met hints over hoe deze weer te geven. Oorspronkelijk was het ontworpen om symboolbibliotheken te maken voor de toepassing KXStitch, maar andere toepassingen gebruiken gelijksoortige functionaliteiten zouden deze ook kunnen gebruiken. Er zijn een aantal hulpmiddelen om het ontwerpen van symbolen te ondersteunen, inclusief lijnen, bezier-krommen, rechthoeken en ellipsen. Teksttekens kunnen geselecteerd worden uit elk lettertype en de symbolen kunnen gespiegeld of gedraaid worden. Symbolen kunnen wel of niet gevuld zijn, de stijl en het type van het lijneinde en het samenvoegen kan gewijzigd worden en de dikte van een lijn kan gevarieerd worden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">SymbolEditor er eit program som kan laga bibliotek av QPainterPath-objekt med hint om korleis dei skal visast. Programmet var opphavleg laga for symbolbibliotek til krosstingprogrammet KXStitch, men andre program som brukar liknande funksjonar kan òg bruka det. Det inneheld fleire nyttige verktøy for teikning av symbol, for eksempel linjer, glatte kurver, rektanglar og ellipsar. Det er òg mogleg å spegelvenda eller dreia symbola og å henta inn teikn frå ulike skrifter. Symbola kan vera fylte eller tomme, og det er mogleg å endra linjebreidd og stilen på linjeendar og linjehjørne.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">EdytorSymboli jest programem do tworzenia bibliotek obiektów QPainterPath z informacjami o sposobie ich wyświetlania. Pierwotnie miał to być program do tworzenia bibliotek symboli dla KXStitch, lecz inne aplikacje potrzebujące podobnej funkcjonalności także mogą go używać. Wspomaganie tworzenia symboli odbywa się poprzez liczne narzędzia takie jak: linie, krzywe sklejane, prostokąty i elipsy. Można wybierać znaki tekstowe oraz symbole z dowolnej czcionki. Następnie można je odbić lustrzenie lub obrócić. Symbole mogą być z wypełnieniem lub nie, można określić rodzaj zakończenia, a także połączenia. Można zmieniać szerokość linii.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Editor de Símbolos é um programa que poderá criar bibliotecas de objectos QPainterPath com sugestões de desenho dos mesmos. Foi originalmente desenhado para criar bibliotecas de símbolos para a aplicação KXStitch, mas outras aplicações que usem uma funcionalidade semelhante também poderão tirar partido delas. Existe um conjunto de ferramentas para ajudar no desenho dos símbolos, incluindo linhas, curvas Bézier, rectângulos e elipses. Os caracteres de texto poderão ser seleccionados a partir de qualquer tipo de letra e os símbolos poderão ser invertidos ou rodados. Os símbolos poderão também ser preenchidos ou não, poder-se-á modificar o tipo de extremidades e das junções e a espessura das linhas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O Editor de Símbolos é um programa que permite criar bibliotecas de objetos QPainterPath com sugestões de como desenhá-los. Foi originalmente projetado para criar bibliotecas de símbolos para o aplicativo KXStitch, mas outros aplicativos que usem uma funcionalidade semelhante também poderão usá-lo. Existe um conjunto de ferramentas para ajudar no desenho de símbolos, incluindo linhas, curvas Bézier, retângulos e elipses. Os caracteres de texto podem ser selecionados a partir de qualquer fonte e os símbolos poderão ser invertidos ou rotacionados. Os símbolos também podem ser preenchidos ou não, e o tipo de extremidade, junções e a espessura das linhas podem ser modificados.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">SymbolEditor je program, ki lahko ustvari knjižnice predmetov QPainterPath z namigi, kako jih upodobiti. Prvotno je bil zasnovan za ustvarjanje knjižnice simbolov za aplikacijo KXStitch, vendar bi aplikacije, ki imajo podobno funkcionalnost lahko to prav tako izkoristila. Obstaja več orodij za oblikovanje simbolov, vključno s črtami, Bezierovimi krivuljami, pravokotniki in elipse. Lahko izberete tudi besedilne znake v katerikoli pisavi in simboli se lahko zrcalijo ali zasukajo. Simboli so lahko napolnjeni ali nepolnjeni, vrsta konca in slog spajanja lahko spremenite, debelina linije pa lahko zelo raznolika.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Symboleditor är ett program som kan skapa bibliotek av QPainterPath-objekt med tips om hur de ska återges. Det konstruerades ursprungligen för att skapa symbolbibliotek för programmet KXStitch, men andra program som använder liknande funktionalitet skulle också kunna använda sig av dem. Det finns ett antal verktyg för att hjälpa till att skapa symboler, inklusive linjer, Bezier-kurvor, rektanglar och ellipser. Texttecken kan väljas från godtyckligt teckensnitt, linjeändar och sammanfogningsstil kan ändras, och linjebredden kan varieras.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">SymbolEditor, nasıl gerçekleneceğine dair ipucu içeren QPainterPath nesneleri kitaplıkları oluşturabilen bir programdır. Aslında KXStitch uygulaması için sembol kitaplıkları oluşturmak için tasarlanmıştı fakat benzer özellikteki diğer uygulamalar da kullanabilir. Sembol tasarlamak için çizgi, bezier eğrisi, dikdörtgen ve elipsi de içeren bir takım araçlar vardır. Herhangi bir yazı tipiden metin karakterler ve sembolller döndürülebilir ya da aynalanabilir. Semboller doldurulabilir ya da doldurulmayabilir, çizgi bitiş türü ve birleştirme biçem değiştirilebilir ve çizgi kalınlığı değişken olabilir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">SymbolEditor — програма для створення бібліотек об’єктів QPainterPath з інструкціями щодо їхнього показу. Програма створювалася для редагування бібліотек позначок програми KXStitch, втім, нею можна скористатися для редагування бібліотек позначок будь-якої іншої програми із подібними функціональними можливостями. Для створення позначок у програмі передбачено декілька інструментів, зокрема інструмент малювання прямих ліній, інструмент малювання кривих Безьє, інструмент малювання прямокутників та інструмент малювання еліпсів. Можна вибрати символи з будь-якого шрифту, обертати та віддзеркалювати створені позначки. Можна створювати заповнені і незаповнені контури, вибирати тип кінчика лінії та тип з’єднання ліній, а також змінювати товщину ліній.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxSymbolEditor is a program that can create libraries of QPainterPath objects with hints on how to render them. It was originally designed to create symbol libraries for the KXStitch application, but other applications using similar functionality could also make use of them. There are a number of tools to aid the designing of symbols, including lines, bezier curves, rectangle and ellipse. Text characters can be selected from any font and the symbols can be mirrored or rotated. Symbols can be filled or unfilled, the line end type and joining style can be changed and the line thickness can be varied.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Funktionen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Funciones:</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Omadused:</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Ezaugarriak:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Ominaisuuksia:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Fitur:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Funzionalità:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">기능:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Kenmerken:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Funksjonar:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Możliwości:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Caracteristici:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Возможности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Zmožnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Özellikler:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Creation of multiple libraries</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Creació de múltiples biblioteques</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Creació de múltiples biblioteques</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Erstellung mehrerer Bibliotheken</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Creation of multiple libraries</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Creación de bibliotecas múltiples</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Mitme teegi loomine</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Liburutegi ugari sortzea</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Useamman kirjaston luonti</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Création de plusieurs bibliothèques</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Creación de varias bibliotecas.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Penciptaan pustaka yang multipel</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Creazione di librerie multiple</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">다양한 라이브러리 만들기</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Maken van meerdere bibliotheken</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Kan laga fleire symbolbibliotek</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Tworzenie wielu bibliotek</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Criação de diversas bibliotecas</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Criação de diversas bibliotecas</li>
      <li xml:lang="ro">Crearea bibliotecilor multiple</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Ustvarjanje več knjižnic</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Kan skapa flera bibliotek</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Çoklu kitaplık oluşumu</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Створення набору бібліотек.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCreation of multiple librariesxx</li>
      <li>Filled and unfilled symbols</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Símbols farcits i no farcits</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Símbols farcits i no farcits</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Gefüllte und ungefüllte Symbole</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Filled and unfilled symbols</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Símbolos rellenos y sin rellenar</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Täidetud ja täitmata sümbolid</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Sinbolo beteak eta betegarririk gabeak</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Täytetyt tai ääriviivasymbolit</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Symboles pleins et non pleins</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Símbolos enchidos e sen encher.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Simbol-simbol terisi dan takterisi</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Simboli riempiti e svuotati</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">채워지거나 채워지지 않은 기호</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Gevulde en niet gevulde symbolen</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Fylde og tomme symbol</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Symbole z wypełnieniem i bez</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Símbolos preenchidos e não preenchidos</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Símbolos preenchidos e não preenchidos</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Zapolnjeni in nezapolnjeni simboli</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Ifyllda och ihåliga symboler</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Doldurulmuş ve doldurulmamış semboller</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Створення заповнених і незаповнених позначок.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFilled and unfilled symbolsxx</li>
      <li>Variable line widths, end types and join types</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Amplades de línia, tipus de final i tipus d'unió variables</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Amplades de línia, tipus de final i tipus d'unió variables</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Variable Linienstärke, Linienenden und -Verbindungen</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Variable line widths, end types and join types</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Anchos de línea, remates y juntas variables</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Arvukalt joonepikkusi, tiputüüpe ja ühendusetüüpe</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Lerro zabalera, erremate mota eta lotura mota aldakorrak</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Vaihtelevan viivan paksuudet sekä pääte- ja liitostyypit</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Largeurs de ligne variables, types de fin et type de fusion</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Anchura de liña variábel, tipos de vértice e de unión.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Lebar garis variabel, tipe ujung dan tipe gabung</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Linee a larghezza variabile, tipi di fine e di unione</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">다양한 선 폭, 끝과 결합 형식</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Variabele lijnbreedte, eindsoorten en samenvoegsoorten</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Ulike breidder og hjørne- og endestilar for linjer</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Zmienne szerokości linii, rodzaje zakończeń i połączeń</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Espessuras de linhas, tipos de extremidades e junções variáveis</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Espessuras de linhas, tipos de extremidades e junções variáveis</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Različne širine črt, koncev črt in vrst spajanja</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Variabla linjebredder, ändtyper och sammanfogningstyper</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Değişken çizgi genişliği, bitiş türleri ve birleştirme türleri</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Різна товщина ліній, різні типи кінців та різні типи з’єднання.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxVariable line widths, end types and join typesxx</li>
      <li>Drag and drop from one library to another</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Arrossegar i deixar anar des d'una biblioteca a una altra</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Arrossegar i deixar anar des d'una biblioteca a una altra</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Ziehen und Ablegen (Drag and Drop) zwischen Bibliotheken</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Drag and drop from one library to another</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Arrastrar y soltar de una biblioteca a otra</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Ühest teegist teise lohistamine</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Arrastatu eta jaregin liburutegi batetik bestera.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Vedä ja pudota kirjastosta toiseen</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Glissez et déposez d'une bibliothèque à une autre</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Arrastrar e soltar dunha biblioteca a outra.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Seret dan taruh dari salahsatu pustaka ke lainnya</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Trascina da una libreria ad un'altra</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">라이브러리간 드래그 앤 드롭</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Verslepen en loslaten uit de ene bibliotheek naar een andere</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Dra og slepp mellom bibliotek</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Przeciąganie i upuszczanie z jednej biblioteki do innej</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Arrastar e largar de uma biblioteca para outra</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Arrastar e soltar de uma biblioteca para outra</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Vlečenje in spuščanje iz ene knjižnice v drugo</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Dra och släpp från ett bibliotek till ett annat</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Bir kitaplıktan diğerine sürükle ve bırak</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Перетягування зі скиданням з однієї бібліотеки до іншої бібліотеки.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxDrag and drop from one library to anotherxx</li>
      <li>Symbol creation from characters</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Creació de símbols des de caràcters</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Creació de símbols des de caràcters</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Symbol-Erstellung aus Zeichen</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Symbol creation from characters</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Creación de símbolos a partir de caracteres</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Sümboli loomine märgi põhjal</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Karaktereen ikurrak sortzea</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Symbolin luonti merkeistä</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Création de symboles à partir de caractères</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Creación de símbolos a partir de caracteres.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Penciptaan simbol dari karakter</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Creazione di simboli da caratteri</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">글자에서 기호 만들기</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Maken van symbolen uit tekens</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Symbollaging basert på teikn</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Tworzenie symboli ze znaków</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Criação de símbolos a partir de caracteres</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Criação de símbolos a partir de caracteres</li>
      <li xml:lang="ro">Crearea simbolurilor din caractere</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Ustvarjanje simbolov iz znakov</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Symboler kan skapas från tecken</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Karakterlerden sembol oluşturma</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Створення позначок із символів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSymbol creation from charactersxx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://userbase.kde.org/Special:myLanguage/SymbolEditor</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=SymbolEditor</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/?application=SymbolEditor</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/symboleditor/symboleditor.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>SymbolEditor</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
